<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts - 毛哥EM的筆記 EM's Notes</title><link>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on 毛哥EM的筆記 EM's Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/1ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/1ac/</guid><description>1AC :::info Resolved: The Taiwanese government should reinstate mandatory one-year military conscription. :::
上次比賽用的1AC可參考寫法或複製格式 | Mind Map | Marktext Download
Good morning honorable judges and distinguished debaters. As the affirmative team, we believed the Taiwanese government should reinstate mandatory one-year military conscription.
I want to start by ranging the stakeholders. According to the &amp;ldquo;Act of Military Service System,&amp;rdquo; males in Taiwan without disabilities or mental disorders who are eligible for physical examination Aged between 18~36 males should have the obligation to receive military service for one year.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/1nc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/1nc/</guid><description>1NC 國防部官網
:::info Resolved: That the Taiwanese government should reinstate mandatory one-year military conscription. :::
Good morning honorable judges and distinguished debaters. As the opposing team, the Taiwanese government shouldn&amp;rsquo;t reinstate mandatory one-year military conscription.
Before I start my debate, I have to admit that Taiwan is facing instability in the Indo-Pacific and a low birthrate. But I think extending military service to one year is a terrible idea, and the situation still has advantages.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/2ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/2ac/</guid><description>2AC :::info Resolved: The Taiwanese government should reinstate mandatory one-year military conscription. :::
Good afternoon, honorable judges and fellow debaters. The affirmative would like to refute the opposing argument with the aff plan.
Increase budget Accroding our budget of military this year ,our defense spending per soldier,defense expenditure per capita and defense spending as a percentage of GDP are all lower than other countries.Alothough the government announces defense spending to rise to 2.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/nc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edit-mr.github.io/notes/posts/cicero2022/nc/</guid><description>1NC Resolved: That the Taiwanese government shouldn’t reinstate mandatory one-year military conscription.
Good morning honorable judges and distinguished debaters. As the opposing team, we think that the taiwanese government shouldn’t reinstate mandatory one-year military conscription.
Before I start my debate, I have to admit that Taiwan is facing instability in the Indo-Pacific and the low birthrate.But I think extending military service to one year is a terrible idea. Next, I will show you the downsides of one-year military service and our solutions to the problems that four-month military service creates.</description></item></channel></rss>